## Piotr Zacha

I am a graduate of the Warsaw University of Technology, where I obtained a master's degree in mechatronics engineering. During my studies, I was dealing, among others, with image processing in C ++. Currently, I focused on developing Python projects covering web-development (Django, Flask), mathematical modeling (NumPy, Matplotlib) and data processing (Pandas, Jupyter Notebook). While still a student, I started working at the Space Research Center of the PAS. I also participated in international trainings organized by the European Space Agency.

After gaining experience as an application engineer at FEV Polska, I decided to continue career in the IT industry. I enjoy new challenges and working in groups. I am willing to share knowledge and learn from more experienced people.







portfolio



linkedin.com/in/piotr-zacha

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Software Application Engineer**

#### FEV Polska

10/2018 - 02/2020

Cracow, Poland

- Development and implementation of MORPHEE automation system components for engines and vehicles test benches,
- developing Python scripts for MORPHEE automation tests generating and modyfing data (logs, csv),
- development of Simulink model,
- working alongside German customer (on/off-site),
- participation in Polish-German-French projects,
- commissioning the projects (hardware and software tests),
- working in international environment.

#### **Intern Engineer**

# Space Research Centre of the Polish Academy of Sciences

04/2017 - 08/2018

Warsaw, Poland

Space Mechatronics and Robotics Laboratory

- Analysis of the impact of flexible antenna (part of Radio Frequency Analyser, used, among others, in <u>JUICE</u> and Chang'E-4 projects) on the dynamics of a spacecraft - creating a mathematical model.
- Matlab and Simulink simulations,
- comparing results with laboratory experiments,
- modeling of mechanical elements (Inventor) JUICE project.

Contact: Tomasz Barciński, PhD – tbarcinski@cbk.waw.pl, +48 22 4966

#### **Student internship**

## Space Research Centre of the Polish Academy of Sciences

07/2016

Warsaw, Poland

Laboratory of Photonics and Micromechanics

Research and analysis of compact Fourier spectrometers.

Contact: Mirosław Rataj, PhD - rataj@cbk.waw.pl

#### Founding member

#### Stowarzyszenie Port Szczecin

09/2017

Szczecin, Poland

Organizing cultural events. Among others, it included:

- coordination of events,
- establishing cooperation with partners,
- member of the audit committee.

 $Contact:\ mgr\ Justyna\ Majzel-stowarzy szenie portszczec in @\ gmail.com$ 

#### **SKILLS**

**Programming** Python, C++, Matlab

Data Science SQL, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas,

Jupyter Notebook, scikit-learn

Web Development Django, Flask, Bootstrap, CSS,

HTML

Other Confluence, JIRA, Git

#### **FOREIGN LANGUAGES**

English

••••

German

## •••00

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Warsaw University of Technology**

BSc and MSc in Mechatronics (full-time), specialization: Photonics Engineering

10/2013 - 07/2018

- MSc thesis: Analysis of the impact of flexible antenna on the dynamics of a spacecraft – in association with SRC PAN.
- BSc thesis: Analysis and modeling of compact Fourier spectrometers.

#### **European Space Agency**

# ESA/ELGRA Gravity-Related Research Summer School 2017

06/2017

ESEC, Belgium

Week-long international summer school. It offered an overview of current research under microgravity and hypergravity conditions in both life and physical sciences.

### **SOFTWARE PROJECTS**

#### **Event calendar**

App that allows to view and manage cultural events. (Django, Bootstrap, HTML)

#### Solar system model

2D Solar system model. User can add additional objects to simulation.

(NumPy, Matplotlib, Tkinter)

#### Blog

(Flask, Bootstrap, SQLAlchemy, HTML)

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).